uniteforsight.org 2006-12-06

# Unite For Sight, Inc. - Privacy Policy

Unite For Sight values your support, and we are committed to protecting your privacy. The purpose of this statement is to share with you our policy concerning your privacy. 

You may use the Unite For Sight web site without disclosing personally identifiable information. We want to be clear that we will not obtain such information about you unless you choose to submit it to us by using our contact form. If you do send us your mailing address or telephone number, we will use it only to contact you regarding a request you have made. We do not share your personal information with telemarketing centers or make telephone solicitations.

When you visit our site, we do collect some non-identifying basic information. This includes total number of visitors, pages viewed and the domain name originating the request. We use this information to improve our site and to make your experience on our web site as smooth as possible. This information may be kept for an indefinite amount of time, and may be used at any time and in any way necessary.

Please note that we do not use "cookies," which are small files stored on your computer's hard drive that are used to track personal information.

This site contains links to other sites. Unite For Sight has no control over the content or the availability of these sites, and is not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites.

Any data you enter on this site will reside on our office computer network, with access limited to the Unite For Sight Board of Directors.

We will not cede or sell your data for any commercial use, or for any use that is not directly linked to our activities or to the use for which you have entered the data.

You have the right to know, correct or cancel your personal data as held on our systems. Please contact [JStaple@uniteforsight.org](mailto:JStaple@uniteforsight.org)
